Brother, what can I do?
uh
Brother, I will do the article.
Still, please give it a try.
Infinite hands holding beer glasses
They say it too much
27 years of solo life
my first kiss
It was you
Since when did you sleep like this?
last month
Why did I get it when I changed my cell phone?
why didn't i know
I didn’t wear them when I exercised because they were uncomfortable.
Still, I got full sometimes.
Pay attention to me
Let's sleep, will it be salty? Salty
Hey
you
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
no no
I'll go alone
It's okay
uh
I want to go home
No, of course I have to take you there.
We live in the same house
Let's go together
Hey
I think you're pretty drunk too.
Then I have two people
I'll bring them all to you.
safely
What do you believe in that?
A co-worker that anyone can trust
Wouldn't I be better?
You're not even my co-worker anymore.
and
Something trustworthy
That's right
So
Who will take me there?
I
I can go alone just fine.
ha
sorry
No, what are we, soldiers?
Why are you walking this like a march?
If you don't want to, just walk behind me.
Oh well, why don’t you go home?
Ah
uh
But the team leader’s house
Isn’t it over there?
I'm passing that way anyway.
Is that so?
Oh, I arrived
Then let's go
Next time, take me to your house
I'm not giving it
How about something delicious at home?
Good
Doesn't Mr. Dohwa's opinion matter?
No, not at your house.
I asked to go to Dohwa’s house.
We'll talk about that later and then we'll go.
again
Shouldn't we rest again?
Please enter carefully.
Don't fall again
Go in carefully.
Go in
why
What should I do? I'll do it.
If I tie it like this, it keeps coming loose.
It's like this every time
Why are you so close?
It's hot, it's hot
my
See you tomorrow
who is it
What the heck
To hit me with that
Ah
Hey, you come when you come
Don't say anything
Why are you so busy?
You won't even answer the phone
uh
Oh sorry
I was with Doa oppa.
Oh doa
I have to go say hello to my brother.
Or should I have a drink for the first time in a while?
Hey, he's already drunk
You two drank alcohol
uh
Hey
He’s all grown up, he’s all grown up, my mother’s son
Hey kid, I'm your brother
Then I'll go check further.
Hey kid, what are you checking?
Ah, go at this time
What are you trying to do because he already drank alcohol?
No, wait a minute
Ah
Oh hello
Hey
Earlier
They said they left but they didn’t even answer the phone
Do you go diving?
Something happened
sorry
I said it was my birthday and now
uh
The cake was all melted too.
Jeon Yeon-sang said she gave up her birthday.
Hey, are you in a relationship?
I'm sorry
I'll buy you some food next time
When the team leader
Wasn't it the other side?
But the team leader’s house
Isn’t it over there?
I'm passing this way anyway.
If I tie it like this, it keeps coming loose.
It's like this every time
Hello, what are you doing in Korea?
I came here briefly because it was vacation.
I keep standing like this
Come in, come in
salty
Wow, it's been a while.
Crazy guy's speaking habits
It's still rough
Ah
That's right, my brother grew up very nicely.
take this rough
How to live in the world
Well, I have a reliable guard dog.
I knew it before
That's what my mom said back then
If you're tired
It will get better
Someone got a message at this time
Oh just
My younger brother knows the team leader of my previous company.
Did you go in well?
Oh, you didn't drink alcohol together.
Yeah
why
Just curious
But
Did you get along well with men?
Do you text something like that?
um
I usually don't do it well
ha
Ah
I am today
It's been a while since I enjoyed a night in Korea.
Because I might not come in
Don't look for it
Don't even call me
I'm going
Hey
Seed your hands
It's okay
I think I like the hand
Uh why
I'm going to go get some water
Earlier
Just when
in the yard
What were you thinking?
I guess you were drunk, but you weren’t.
Yudoah
uh
you
기억났지
What are you talking about?
기억났잖아
curse
조심해야죠
thank you i'm fine
유도 가자 어
타이밍
It's good
야 그니까 내가
I told you to drink in moderation.
Ah, thank you, come down
you
uh
그 사람 좋아해
who
Team leader
Yeah
What are you talking about?
I decided to buy you food
밥을 사 주셔서 또
밥을 같이 먹기로
You eat with someone every day
uh
I don't think you eat with anyone
I don't like it
지난 날들의
날개를 접고서
That
사고였잖아
Let's pretend it never happened
I don't want to be awkward with you
me
People who like Lee Do-ah
Maybe
Someone confessed, how do you feel?
a little scared
anyone
I'm afraid of getting hurt
Don't worry about towing
that person
Mr. Doha
Do something you haven't done before
I'm going to try it
Doha Lee
I like it a lot